How did the surveillance notice get lost?
Maybe the nanny threw it out by mistake.
Good thing Lawyer Ding found it.
Do you know that without the notice,
how hard it is to find someone?
Thank you.
Here, leave your thumbprint.
Excuse me.
Where is the restroom?
Over there.
Thank you.
Just find one thing at my place,
and I'm sure
you'll find the Sham Litigation Base.
Why?
Turn it over to the Economic Crime Investigation Division,
or Prosecutor's Office. Isn't it faster?
That key
is a spare key to Zhao Yijie's office.
If the police go
and don't find anything,
it'll only tip him off.
So someone from Rujie should sneak in.
Does Zhao Yijie know you have his key?
Of course not.
I secretly made a copy.
So you want me to sneak in
and find clues to this base's location.
The key is to find a car key.
That key of his
is hidden in a picture frame in his office.
For places he fears being followed to,
he uses a spare car.
And that spare vehicle
is in the law firm's underground garage.
You can look up its frequent addresses.
And once you find the car,
whether you check its driving routes
or track its license plate,
you won't be far from finding the base.
Lao Yu.
Ding Ning, I'm right here.
I was just looking for you.
I'll buy some paintbrushes for Awu first.
He's been asking for them for days.
We'll meet over there later.
I bought you breakfast.
Come over and have a bite. Come on.
You bought so much.
I noticed every day when you leave,
you just get an iced coffee,
and just a piece of bread.
You know how important breakfast is.
Come on, come on.
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I bought a bit of everything.
Come on.
Aren't you going to wake Awu up?
Kids need more sleep to grow tall.
Do you want some porridge?
I'll pass. You have it.
I'll have it then.
Here. Take your time eating.
Alright, I'll take my time eating.
You take your time talking.
Go ahead.
You know I got mad at you before.
It was about you joining Rujie.
I've been thinking about it since.
Have you ever thought about
opening your own law firm?
Your own law firm.
We could start an independent firm together.
Think about it.
Having your own law firm,
you could safely and freely
do what you want to do.
Plus,
with me around, you won't lack cases.
We'd have to plan that carefully.
I need to finish my current cases first.
Take Mrs. Lin's case, for example.
That one is easy enough.
But Liang Zidong's case is very complex.
I'm not asking you to quit immediately.
At least wait for me
until my three-year non-compete is up.
Do you remember my mentee, Ma Tingting?
The one at the Prosecutor's Office.
We had a get-together not long ago.
She told me she was exhausted.
I heard she's in a task force
responsible for investigating Fuxia Group.
Do you know what I mean?
In Liang Zidong's case,
they must be investigating Zhao Yijie too.
And his protective umbrella.
That's why I'm telling you,
Rujie really isn't as simple as you think.
Didn't you say it yourself?
Liang Zidong said they have a
Sham Litigation Base, right?
Isn't that place just
a headquarters for criminal activities?
Haven't you thought about reporting it?
I have.
Of course I have.
But I fear it'll be like when I reported you.
I might regret it afterward.
Doing the right thing
at least leaves no regrets.
Look, our relationship
is pretty good now, isn't it?
I think
after you report it,
you can justifiably quit.
And make a much cleaner exit.
Right?
It's just a suggestion,
giving you another option.
You decide what to do yourself.
Are you going to the prison later?
Are you just going to wear that?
Fiancée.
And him?
Son. Adopted.
Is he their child?
No, he's adopted.
It says "adopted" here.
Our rules here state that
only family members can go in.
Understood.
They can go in. I won't.
Alright, you two can go in.
Okay. Thank you.
Awu!
Dad!
Dad misses you.
How could you come here?
You shouldn't have come.
You can't be here.
Why did you come here?
They said I can visit you every month now.
What? What did you say?
Awu, stop crying.
Let's not waste time.
Didn't you have a gift for Dad?
Show it to him.
They taught me how to write.
Look, I wrote this.
They said I wrote it wrong.
But I think
the wrong ones look better than the right.
Okay, okay.
Awu, did they hit you?
They didn't hit me.
Zhao Yijie told me to go to school.
But I don't want to go to school.
They're all very nice.
But I don't like it here.
The trees here are all trimmed the same.
Everyone on the street has the same face.
The animals in the zoo
have the same faces as the people.
It's the same everywhere.
Awu, could you ask Dad
how he got that injury?
How did you get injured?
Dad is fine.
Just got into a fight with a cellmate.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
He got it fighting someone in his cell.
A few months ago,
a male lawyer came to see Dad.
Dad told him about it.
Dad is fine. Really.
He also said that a few months ago,
he mentioned it to a male lawyer
during a meeting at the detention center.
A male lawyer?
Zhou Hao.
Was that male lawyer named Zhou Hao?
Zhou Hao, you lied to me.
Those two days you went missing,
you saw Lao Kang at the detention center, right?
Aren't you handling Mr. Liang's case?
No wonder you've been acting so weird.
And after Lao Kang's case,
you stopped doing criminal law
and switched to civil law under Xu Ruqing.
Until Liang Zidong's case.
We'll talk about this later.
How could...
Mrs. Lin.
Over here.
Lawyer Ding!
Go on, go on.
You haven't gotten off work yet?
Zhou Hao, I'm not done talking!
Lawyer Ding.
Mrs. Lin, I just came back for some files.
My car is still waiting downstairs.
I have to leave right away.
That's all right.
I just came to express my gratitude.
You said you'd give your all to our case.
I thought you were just saying that.
I didn't think you'd get us a court date.
And your defense statement...
It was written perfectly.
I've saved it
to make our kid
recite it word for word.
To let them know
what makes a good essay.
Thank you!
It's my job.
Oh, right.
About the job you helped Lao Lin find,
we've sent you his resume.
Does it look okay?
Resume?
What resume?
The assistant lawyer...
named Zhao... something Jie.
Zhao Yijie.
Right, he told us to send it.
He said
you were helping Lao Lin find a new job,
so we hurried and prepared a resume.
I know
it's not part of your job as a lawyer.
But
you really treat us both as friends
to help us out this much.
Thank you!
Oh, right.
He told us to contact this person
to arrange an interview.
When is the interview?
Kong Dongshun.
Yes.
Let me go check for you.
Please take a seat for a moment.
Okay.
Kong Dongshun.
Is Kong Dongshun a lawyer at our firm?
I've never heard of this person.
Admin?
A driver or an assistant, perhaps?
Look it up.
Why are these all Fuxia civil cases?
Assigned by Director Xu.
Assigned by Xu Ruqing?
Then why are the signatories all interns?
You noticed too.
A couple of days ago, a few interns and I
were wondering about this too.
They let the interns do most of the work.
It's a chance to make some extra cash.
They were all thrilled.
Were you doing this
before I found Liang Zidong
or after?
I've been doing it all along.
I got here before you did, right?
I've been doing it since I arrived.
But after you found Mr. Liang,
these minor cases involving
mortgages, guarantees, and loans
did start to pile up again.
Zhou Hao.
Try not to do these anymore.
If possible,
help the interns back out too.
Does this have to do with Liang Zidong?
I can't be sure right now.
But if it's really what I think it is,
the interns are too inexperienced
to tell
if it involves sham litigation
or forged evidence.
If they really start arresting people,
will they arrest Xu Ruqing?
They'll arrest those of you who signed.
Sham litigation?
That can't be, right?
Many of these cases were filed long ago.
If there really was a problem,
the firm's reputation would be ruined.
Who'd dare hire Rujie after that?
Did you find Kong Dongshun?
No.
I even checked the list of employees
who left in the past few years,
and there's no such person at all.
What's up with him?
I held a concert for a friend's daughter.
Let's go watch it together.
It's nothing.
Please keep an eye on Mrs. Lin for me.
I'm warning you one more time.
Any cases related to Fuxia Group,
stop working on them.
You must back out of this, got it?
I'm not joking with you.
Have you eaten?
Want some?
What's wrong?
I think you're quite conflicted.
What are you talking about?
You came all the way to my house...
just to have a heart-to-heart with me?
I do want to have a heart-to-heart.
Then forget it.
For a heart-to-heart, go find Lao Yu.
About the Sham Litigation Base...
I know about it.
Liang Zidong told you this?
Yes.
Not only did he tell me,
he also asked me to report it,
just like I reported Yu Songfan back then.
They say you're a master manipulator.
But you blew it.
You helped Mrs. Lin's family, who are strangers,
find jobs,
and solved their problems from the root.
You held a concert for Kong Dongshun's daughter,
fulfilling a father's wish.
I guess
you running the Sham Litigation Base
is to save thousands of jobs at Fuxia Group.
Right?
You clearly have things you value deeply.
I know you care about me and Yu Songfan.
You have many people you care about.
But on one hand, you care about us,
and on the other, you're using us.
Aren't you tired of living like this?
I'm really not sure anymore.
I fear it'll be like reporting Yu Songfan.
Because doing something
I thought was right,
ended up hurting innocent people.
I'm also afraid of dragging Rujie down.
Dragging Zhou Hao down.
Dragging down the interns at the firm.
And dragging you down too.
Drag me down?
Are you really that confident now?
How could you drag me down?
Liang Zidong, Yu Songfan,
even Xu Ruqing,
not a single person is on your side.
Everyone wants me to report you.
The more it's like this,
the more I feel things aren't that simple.
I know even if I ask you
what's really hidden behind all this,
you won't tell me.
But at least,
I hope you can stop the sham litigations.
At least walk away from it.
For you,
it might be the best choice.
Stop exhausting yourself, okay?
The Sham Litigation Base cannot stop.
Why?
Why can't you stop?
Since it's come to this,
I'll be honest.
Ding Ning.
Help me just this once, okay?
Don't report it.
Don't you get it?
Even though I don't know
why everyone wants me
to report it,
if you don't want
you and everyone at Rujie to be implicated,
disband the Sham Litigation Base
and leave Fuxia Group alone.
But my guess is, this Sham Litigation Base
will act like a bomb,
blowing your targets to pieces.
And just like Liang Zidong said,
your backers
will be able to hide even deeper.
As for you,
you've become a discarded pawn.
This kid is pretty hard to find.
Yeah.
Here.
Right here.
Lao Fan
Has anyone seen the kid from this family?
Haven't seen him. No idea.
His family works at the construction site.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Hello.
Excuse me, which one is Lu Zhiyong?
Over there.
The shortest one.
Thanks.
Lu Zhiyong!
Stop right there!
Don't run! Stop!
Don't you run!
It wasn't a big deal to begin with.
But running makes it worse.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Get up.
Is your name Lu Zhiyong?
What about it?
You'd better behave.
Or you and your mom will lose your jobs.
I'm talking to him.
We already know all about you.
Your dad fell and was paralyzed at the site.
The site didn't pay you any compensation,
but let you and your mom do odd jobs.
Right?
I didn't do anything wrong.
But you lied about your age to work.
Come back to the station with me first.
We'll hold your boss accountable later.
Take him away.
Let's go. Move.
Your hand is scraped.
Is it serious?
Can we contact your mom?
The site didn't give you compensation,
so you went and stole people's money?
I didn't steal.
What about your friend who was with you?
He didn't steal either.
Why pick a lock into someone's house?
Just to take a look.
Look at what?
At how the house my dad built looks now.
Your dad built it?
Wasn't your dad working at the site
when he fell and got paralyzed?
How could he have built it?
He built lots of buildings before he fell.
Then why did you
push a paralyzed old man
from his home to the police station?
To take him out for some fun.
Why don't you take your dad out?
Why take out an old man you don't know?
He has a wheelchair.
My dad doesn't.
Do you know
that picking a lock is illegal?
Even if you didn't know that,
you should know you'd get caught stealing.
I didn't steal anything.
You're still lying.
The security cameras recorded it all.
And what about your shorter little friend?
What's your friend's name?
Did you give the money you stole
to your mom already?
I didn't steal.
I just went to play.
We found the surveillance footage.
Good.
Think about it carefully.
Contact the community workers.
Four households reported the crime.
Two of them had security cameras.
The footage shows Lu Zhiyong
just walking around looking.
Right before leaving, he even
cleaned up the place a bit.
So he's acting like a cleaning fairy?
What about the other one?
The other one.
Only this one captured both kids.
But because of the angle
and the fact the other kid is too short,
we couldn't get a shot of their face.
We can only rely on you to ask him.
Is there any more?
The rest of the footage is from hallways.
It only proves they picked locks to enter.
There's no way to directly prove
that they committed theft.
I remember at the paralyzed man's house,
his daughter said she lost 2,000 yuan.
Xiao Li's forensics team went to check,
and there were no signs of a break-in.
When they asked again,
the old man's kids finally told the truth.
They didn't lose any money at all.
They didn't lose any money?
So they were trying to extort the kid?
Exactly.
So a theft charge probably won't stick.
Then should we proceed with trespassing
and send it to the Prosecutor's Office?
Let's wait.
First, let's contact the kid's parents
and find the other kid before we decide.
Got it.
It's not that I forgot.
But since I was house-hunting all day
and I had to pick up my kid from school,
I couldn't make it.
Right, I'll meet you tomorrow.
Sorry about that.
Okay.
Take out your homework.
Do your homework first.
And then Grandpa will go cook dinner.
I don't want to do my homework.
I want to watch TV.
How can you do that?
Finish your homework before watching TV.
Be a good boy.
What's wrong?
Why are you throwing a tantrum?
Grandpa will do your homework with you.
It'll be fast.
Right? Grandpa will teach you how.
Come here. Be good.
Do adults have to do homework too?
Of course.
Then I'd rather not grow up.
My teacher was lying after all.
Why?
Today, my teacher said
things get easier when you grow up.
You don't need a backpack anymore.
My classmates all want to grow up.
Some of my classmates
want to be scientists.
Some classmates
want to be athletes.
Some want to be doctors.
They asked me,
"What do you want to be?"
How did you answer?
I said I didn't know.
I definitely don't want to do
the work Zhao Yijie and Ding Ning do.
Because they never come home.
I don't want a job where I can't go home.
Grandpa is the best.
You're home every day.
Grandpa, did you use to work?
What kind of work did you do?
Be good. Grandpa needs to make a call.
Do your homework.
Hello, Lao Wang.
Lao Yu.
Are the results of my medical checkup out?
Not yet.
The results really aren't out.
Your situation is a bit complicated.
Okay, just tell me.
How much time do I have left?
Lao Yu.
Don't add any more
unnecessary stress on yourself.
Think about it.
You've spent your life
standing for fairness and justice,
upright and honest.
Honestly, you've had a good run.
Just enjoy your retirement.
That's better than anything.
Once I have a definitive result,
I'll let you know immediately, okay?
Awu!
Grandpa!
Wake up, Grandpa!
Grandpa, are you okay?
Don't scare me.
Are you okay?
Grandpa!
Hello, Sister Ding Ning.
Come quickly!
Grandpa fainted!
It's just a bit of low blood sugar.
Have something to eat and you'll be fine.
Got it.
You scared Awu to death.
Good thing he called me to come back.
It seems that new car Zhao Yijie gave you
...actually did some good.
Otherwise, how could you have rushed back
...to save me?
I went to see Mrs. Liang a few days ago.
I know where the Sham Litigation Base...
...is located.
Should I ask Ma Tingting out to meet you?
Not right now.
Let me think about it.
By the way.
Have you been hearing cicadas recently?
I'm a bit curious.
Why do you always hear cicadas...
...instead of birds singing...
...or some other sounds?
I find it strange, too.
Maybe it's because my son, Xiao Yue...
...used to talk to me about cicadas a lot.
Actually, cicadas are amazing.
They can lie dormant for twelve years.
Then emerge to molt in the thirteenth.
Only to live for one summer before dying.
Twelve years for a single summer.
I wonder if it's a bad deal.
Can you make a decision tomorrow?
Looking for me?
I called you,
but you didn't answer, as usual.
So I came over here.
So, as usual, you
came straight to my door to confront me.
The last time we met
was about the nursing home case, right?
Yeah, it's a small world.
Go ahead. What is it?
I read the indictment.
On Liang Zidong's case,
you signed for the Prosecutor's Office.
But I'm guessing
you have other colleagues
looking into the Fuxia Group, right?
I know where the Sham Litigation Base is.
But I don't advise making a move now.
Lawyer Ding,
regardless of how many differences
we've had in handling past cases,
I believe
our attitude toward crime
is exactly the same, right?
Hold on.
If you hear me out
and still insist on going,
then I'll help you.
But let's be clear upfront,
I won't be responsible for the fallout.
If you agree, I'll continue.
Let me consult my superiors.
Ding Ning,
you came to me
saying you found
the Sham Litigation Base tied to Fuxia Group.
If this is true,
it means
you've helped us solve a major case.
And for the clues you provided,
we will commend and reward you.
I'm not here to take credit.
I'm here to clear my name.
I just found out
there might be illegal activities,
and I came to report them.
Here to report again.
But I'll repeat myself:
I don't advise making a move now.
What's your reason?
Does none of you think
that this whole thing is very fishy?
Should my people step in?
I think it's better if I go myself.
What do you think?
Mr. Bi,
Go ahead.
In 2019,
when Jiangliu City sought investments,
we set our sights on Fuxia Group.
We wanted them to build a factory here.
It wasn't just us back then. There were
local governments from four other cities
that all wanted them to move there.
They offered all kinds of incentives.
So we took an unconventional approach.
On the surface, it met national policies
regarding their taxes,
fines, and regulations.
But in private, we...
We used taxpayers' money
to subsidize Fuxia Group.
You and I did the math before.
As long as Fuxia was willing to come,
for every ten yuan of public money spent,
we could get 32 yuan back.
The price
was that we all broke the laws and rules.
But since 2019,
Fuxia Group has been going downhill.
Not only do they bring us no benefits,
but because of environmental issues,
they've become a burden we can't shake.
Mr. Bi,
must a burden
be destroyed?
The survival of Fuxia Group
affects
the families and jobs of 10,000 employees.
In our position,
we must consider the long term.
I know why you can't bring yourself to.
Because once you do,
it means
all the hardships you've endured,
the grievances you've suffered,
and the risks you've taken
will all be meaningless.
However,
Fuxia Group has now
become an obstacle to our development.
We must abandon it.
Going to see Yu Songfan again.
I knew you weren't the type
to be so stubborn.
I'm glad you're back.
Otherwise, with such a big operation,
someone needs to be in charge, right?
Now I can go back to slacking off.
Slacking off?
Maybe another day.
You still have to go tonight.
How did it go?
Is Ding Ning willing to go?
Shouldn't be a problem.
Did you need me for something?
You must personally
place this in the Sham Litigation Base.
Is this more material
to frame some director or president?
If you really want to join us,
ask what you should ask,
and don't ask what you shouldn't.
When do you want me to put it in?
I haven't decided yet, actually.
Tell you what,
wait for my word.
Once I find the right opportunity,
I'll call to let you know.
Okay.
Also, take this.
It's a gift from an elder.
This is for Yang Awu,
a growth policy from an offshore bank.
Once the kid turns eighteen,
the bank will pay him 50,000 a year,
until you two reunite in heaven.
Anything else?
Thank you.
Assistant Xiao Zhao, at your service.
Where are you going?
Let's chat.
Come here.
Thank you.
You're right.
As for me,
I blew the act.
If you don't report the Sham Litigation Base,
or just drop Liang Zidong's case,
I'll be the one to lose the most,
not you.
Actually, after meeting you and Lao Yu,
I suddenly realized
that I've been exhausted all along,
but I didn't know how to rest.
What exactly are you trying to say?
I want to try something,
which is opening up to someone.
I want you to help me see
if the first half of my life
was meaningful at all,
and if everything I've done
is completely worthless.
Ding Ning.
What do you think of Chang Yu?
You know Chang Yu?
More than that.
He was once one of the founders of Rujie.